Register of the Leopold Labedz papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Writings by Others, 1921-1987
  - Lyon, David N., 1977 (Box-folder 105: 8)
  - Mack, Charles L., 1971 (Box-folder 105: 9)
  - Mackintosh, M., undated (Box-folder 105: 10)
  - Macoveanu, Petre, undated (Box-folder 105: 11)
  - Madsen, Mark H., 1979 (Box-folder 105: 12)
  - Magocsi, Paul R., 1974 (Box-folder 105: 13)
  - Malcher, George, 1985 (Box-folder 105: 14)
  - Malcolm, Neil, undated (Box-folder 105: 15)
  - Malinowski, Jan, undated (Box-folder 105: 16)
  - Mancall, Mark, undated (Box-folder 105: 17)
  - Mandak, Jan, 1977 (Box-folder 105: 18)
  - Manne, Robert, 1975 (Box-folder 105: 19)
  - Marchenko, A., undated (Box-folder 105: 20)
  - Marianski, Antoni, 1986 (Box-folder 105: 21)
  - Marshall, Richard H., 1967 (Box-folder 105: 22)
  - Martin, L. W., undated (Box-folder 106: 1)
  - Mason, David S., 1985 (Box-folder 106: 2)
  - Mason, Warren L., 1979 (Box-folder 106: 3)
  - Masters, Anthony, 1974 (Box-folder 106: 4)
  - Matejko, Aleksander, 1972, undated (Box-folder 106: 5-6)
  - Mathewson, Rufus, undated (Box-folder 106: 7)
  - Mathieu, Vittorio, 1975 (Box-folder 106: 8)
  - Mayne, Richard, undated (Box-folder 106: 9)
  - Maximov, V. E., 1975 (Box-folder 106: 10)
  - Mazuri, Ali A., 1976 (Box-folder 106: 11)
  - McCagg, William, 1971 (Box-folder 106: 12)
  - McDonald, John W., 1974-1975 (Box-folder 106: 13)
  - McInnes, Neil, 1971 (Box-folder 106: 14)
  - McKay, Reynolds, 1972 (Box-folder 106: 15)
  - Mead, Gary, undated (Box-folder 107: 1)
  - Medvedev, Zhores A., undated (Box-folder 107: 2)
  - Meijer, 1961 (Box-folder 107: 3)
  - Melchuk, Igor, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 107: 4)
  - Melis, George S., 1970 (Box-folder 107: 5)
  - Menon, P. K., 1974 (Box-folder 107: 6)
  - Merton, Alan, 1969 (Box-folder 107: 7)
  - Mesa-Lago, Carmelo, 1971 (Box-folder 107: 8)
  - Messmer, William B., 1979 (Box-folder 107: 9)
  - Metcalf, A., 1986 (Box-folder 107: 10)
  - Meyrick, S. J., undated (Box-folder 107: 11)
  - Mianowicz, Tomasz, undated (Box-folder 107: 12)
  - Michnik, Adam, undated (Box-folder 107: 13)
  - Mihajlov, Mihajlo, 1980 (Box-folder 107: 14)
  - Mikheyev, Dmitry, 1985 (Box-folder 107: 15)
  - Mikulak, Maxim, undated (Box-folder 107: 16)
  - Miles, undated (Box-folder 107: 17, Box-folder 108: 1)
  - Miller, Jacob, 1967 (Box-folder 108: 2)
  - Miller, James R., 1971 (Box-folder 108: 3)
  - Milosz, Czeslaw, undated (Box-folder 108: 4)
  - Minc, Julia, 1985 (Box-folder 108: 5)
  - Misztal, Bronislaw, 1983 (Box-folder 108: 6)
  - Moczarski, Kazimierz, 1978 (Box-folder 108: 7)
  - de Molenes, 1971 (Box-folder 108: 8)
  - Monditsch, M., 1965 (Box-folder 108: 9)
  - Mondolfo, Rodolfo, 1967 (Box-folder 108: 10)
  - Montias, J. M., 1973 (Box-folder 108: 11)
  - Morales, Juan Jorge, 1980 (Box-folder 108: 12)
  - Morawska, Ewa, Poland: Holding a Bear (Casimir Garnysh) by the Tail, undated (Box-folder 108: 13)
  - Morawska, Ewa, 1987 (Box-folder 108: 14)
  - Morawski, Dominik, undated (Box-folder 108: 15)
  - Morgan, Patrick, 1985 (Box-folder 108: 16)
  - Morgenthau, Hans J., undated (Box-folder 108: 17)
  - Morris, Stephan J., undated (Box-folder 108: 18)
  - Moscow, Taylor, undated (Box-folder 109: 1)
  - Mujal-Leon, Eusebio M., 1978 (Box-folder 109: 2)
  - Muller, David G., Jr., 1974 (Box-folder 109: 3)
  - Murphy, Patrick W., 1972-1973 (Box-folder 109: 4)
  - Myers, Kenneth A., 1975 (Box-folder 109: 5)
  - Nagy-Talavera, Nicholas M., 1970 (Box-folder 109: 6)
  - Najder, Zdzislaw, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 109: 7)
  - Nathan, James A., 1976-1978 (Box-folder 109: 8)
  - Navrozov, Lev, circa 1980 (Box-folder 109: 9)
  - Nelson, Daniel N., 1976 (Box-folder 109: 10)
  - Nettler, Ronald L., undated (Box-folder 109: 11)
  - Neznansky, Friedrich, 1978 (Box-folder 109: 12)
  - Nitze, Paul H., 1985 (Box-folder 109: 13)
  - Noorani, A. G., 1975 (Box-folder 109: 14)
  - Norr, Henry, 1984 (Box-folder 109: 15)
  - Nowak, Jan, undated (Box-folder 109: 16)
  - Nowak, Leszek, undated (Box-folder 109: 17)
  - Nowakowski, Marek, undated (Box-folder 109: 18)
  - Nowakowski, Tadeusz, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 109: 19)
  - Nutsch, James G., undated (Box-folder 109: 20)
  - Nyman, I., 1977 (Box-folder 109: 21)
  - O'Brien, Patrick, 1974 (Box-folder 110: 1)
  - Ogunbadejo, Oye, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 110: 2)
  - Oja, Matt F., 1985 (Box-folder 110: 3)
  - Okroi, Loren J., 1981 (Box-folder 110: 4)
  - Olecki, Alexander, undated (Box-folder 110: 5)
  - Orvik, Karen Erickson, undated (Box-folder 110: 6)
  - Owen, Richard, undated (Box-folder 110: 7)
  - Ozernoy, Vladimir M., 1985 September (Box-folder 110: 8)
  - Pajak, Roger F., 1979 (Box-folder 110: 9)
  - Pakulski, Jan, 1980 (Box-folder 110: 10)
  - Palmegiano, E. M., 1980 (Box-folder 110: 11)
  - Palmer, S. T., 1969 (Box-folder 110: 12)
  - Palladin, A., 1985 (Box-folder 110: 13)
  - Parchomenko, Walter, 1984 (Box-folder 110: 14)
  - Pasquino, Gianfranco, 1979 (Box-tape 110: 15)
  - Paterson, W. E., 1972 (Box-folder 110: 16)
  - Pawlak, Jan, undated (Box-folder 110: 17)
  - Payne, Richard J., undated (Box-folder 110: 18)
  - Pennar, Jaan, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 110: 19)
  - Perelman, Chaim, 1975 (Box-folder 110: 20)
  - Peri, Yoram, undated (Box-folder 110: 21)
  - Peterson, William, 1975 (Box-folder 110: 22)
  - Petriccione, Sandro, undated (Box-folder 110: 23)
  - Petrilli, M. Guiseppe, 1973 (Box-folder 111: 1)
  - Petro, Nicolai N., 1984-1986 (Box-folder 111: 2)
  - Petursson, Eric, 1986 (Box-folder 111: 3)
  - Philonenko, Alexis, 1975 (Box-folder 111: 4)
  - Pickering, C. R., 1976 (Box-folder 111: 5)
  - Pierre, Andrew J., undated (Box-folder 111: 6)
  - Pilon, Juliana Geran, 1984 (Box-folder 111: 7)
  - Pinder, John, 1968 (Box-folder 111: 8)
  - Pipes, Richard, undated (Box-folder 111: 9)
  - Ploss, Sidney, 1984 (Box-folder 111: 10)
  - Podgorecki, A., 1980 (Box-folder 111: 11)
  - Podhoretz, Norman, 1986 (Box-folder 111: 12)
  - Polonsky, Anthony, undated (Box-folder 111: 13)
  - Pomazov, Vitali, undated (Box-folder 111: 14)
  - Pomerantsev, Igor, 1978 (Box-folder 111: 15)
  - Pontuso, James F., 1986-1987 (Box-folder 111: 16)
  - Porket, J. L., 1974-1975 (Box-folder 111: 17)
  - Pospielovsky, Dimitry, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 111: 18)
  - Potichnyj, Peter J., 1970 (Box-folder 111: 19)
  - Preisner, Rio, 1978 (Box-folder 112: 1)
  - des Pres, Terrance, undated (Box-folder 112: 2)
  - Prybyla, J. S., 1977 (Box-folder 112: 3)
  - Quinlan, Paul D., 1979 (Box-folder 112: 4)
  - Raftery, John M., 1974 (Box-folder 112: 5)
  - Rahman, H., 1970 (Box-folder 112: 6)
  - Rajski, Marian, 1982 (Box-folder 112: 7)
  - Rakowska-Harmstone, Teresa, 1977, undated (Box-folder 112: 8-10)
  - Raphael, D. D., 1975 (Box-folder 112: 11)
  - Ray, Hemen, undated (Box-folder 112: 12)
  - Raymond, Paul D., 1977 (Box-folder 112: 13)
  - Reddaway, Peter, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 112: 14)
  - Reisch, Alfred A., 1985 (Box-folder 113: 1)
  - Rejai, Mostafa, 1978 (Box-folder 113: 2)
  - Remington, Robin A., 1968 (Box-folder 113: 3)
  - Representative Government and National Progress, undated (Box-folder 113: 4-5)
    A collaborative report from a conference in Ibadan, Nigeria featuring chapters written by Herbert Passin, St. Clair Drake, S. N. Eisenstadt, David E. Apter, Ayo Agunsheye, Thomas Diop, F. R. A. Williams, K. A. B. Jones-Quartey, Edward Shils, Eme O. Awa, and A. D. Gorwala.
  - Retzlaw, Karl, undated (Box-folder 113: 6-7, 114: 1)
  - Rhoodie, Eschel, 1986 (Box-folder 114: 2)
  - Rittersporn, Gabor T., 1977 (Box-folder 114: 3)
  - Robak, K. R., 1977 (Box-folder 114: 4)
  - Roberts, Paul Craig, 1973 (Box-folder 114: 5)
  - Romaniecki, Leon, undated (Box-folder 114: 6)
  - Romanowski, Jerzy, 1972 (Box-folder 114: 7)
  - Ronay, undated (Box-folder 114: 8)
  - Rooke, Margaret, 1981 (Box-folder 114: 9)
  - Rosenberger, Leif, undated (Box-folder 114: 10)
  - Rosenthal, Harry Kenneth, 1972 (Box-folder 114: 11)
  - Rostow, Eugene, 1978 (Box-folder 114: 12)
  - Roth, David F., 1969 (Box-folder 114: 13)
  - Rovan, Joseph, 1986 (Box-folder 115: 1)
  - Rozek, Edward, 1979 (Box-folder 115: 2)
  - Rozhansky, A., undated (Box-folder 115: 3)
  - Rubinstein, Joshua, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 115: 4)
  - Rudenko-Tykhyi, 1977 (Box-folder 115: 5)
  - Rudner, Martin, undated (Box-folder 115: 6)
  - Rullkotter, Bernd, 1974 (Box-folder 115: 7)
  - Rupnik, Jacques, 1984 (Box-folder 115: 8)
  - Rurarz, Zdzislaw, 1983 (Box-folder 115: 9)
  - Rush, M., 1961 (Box-folder 115: 10)
  - Rustow, Margrite Wreschner, undated (Box-folder 115: 11)
  - Ryavec, Karl W., 1969 (Box-folder 115: 12)
  - Rywkin, Michael, undated (Box-folder 115: 13)
  - Rzhevsky, Leonid, 1976 (Box-folder 115: 14)
  - Sackmann, Peter J., 1982 (Box-folder 115: 15)
  - Sadykiewicz, Michal, 1982 (Box-folder 115: 16, 116: 1-2)
  - Saikal, Amin, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 116: 3-4)
  - Sakharov, Andrei D., undated (Box-folder 116: 5)
  - Salisbury, Harrison E., 1971 (Box-folder 116: 6)
  - Salloch, Roger, 1968 (Box-folder 116: 7)
  - Samal, Mary Hrabik, undated (Box-folder 116: 8)
  - Sanczez-Gijon, Antonio, 1983 (Box-folder 116: 9)
  - Sanders, Sol, 1987 (Box-folder 116: 10)
  - Santolucito, Sandra, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 116: 11)
  - Satter, David, 1982 (Box-folder 116: 12)
  - Sawczuk, Konstantyn, 1980 (Box-folder 116: 13)
  - Sawer, Marian, 1975 (Box-folder 117: 1)
  - Schabert, Tilo, 1975 (Box-folder 117: 2)
  - Schapiro, Leonard, 1969 (Box-folder 117: 3)
  - Scharf, Bradley, 1978 (Box-folder 117: 4)
  - Schatten, Fritz, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 117: 5)
  - Schleimann, Jorgen, undated (Box-folder 117: 6)
  - Schmukler, 1973 (Box-folder 117: 7)
  - Schnytzer, A., 1970 (Box-folder 117: 8)
  - Schoenbaum, David, undated (Box-folder 117: 9)
  - Schopflin, George, undated (Box-folder 117: 10)
  - Schram, Stuart, 1971 (Box-folder 117: 11)
  - Schurer, H., undated (Box-folder 117: 12)
  - Schwartz, Morton, undated (Box-folder 117: 13)
  - Scott, Bryan and Ivor Williams, undated (Box-folder 118: 1)
  - Scott, William F., 1977 (Box-folder 118: 2)
  - Scruton, Roger, 1985 (Box-folder 118: 3)
  - Seabury, Paul, 1973 (Box-folder 118: 4)
  - Sedov, Leonid, 1975 (Box-folder 118: 5)
  - Segal, Boris H., undated (Box-folder 118: 6)
  - Segal, Melinda, 1984 (Box-folder 118: 7)
  - Sejna, Jan, undated (Box-folder 118: 8)
  - Seki, Yoshihiko, 1979 (Box-folder 118: 9)
  - Sellekaerts, Willy, 1970 (Box-folder 118: 10)
  - Seplaki, Les, 1976 (Box-folder 118: 11)
  - de la Serna, Victor, 1985 (Box-folder 118: 12)
  - Seroka, Jim, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 118: 13)
  - Seth, S. P., 1975-1985 (Box-folder 118: 14)
  - Seward, Lydia, 1979 (Box-folder 118: 15)
  - Shafarevich, I. R., 1978-1979 (Box-folder 118: 16)
  - Shaffer, Harry G., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 118: 17)
  - Shafir, Michael, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 118: 18)
  - Shelov, D., undated (Box-folder 119: 1)
  - Sherman, Howard J., 1968 (Box-folder 119: 2)
  - Shils, Edward, undated (Box-folder 119: 3)
  - Shoemaker, Robert W., III, 1972 (Box-folder 119: 4)
  - Shragin, Boris, undated (Box-folder 119: 5)
  - Shtromas, A. Y. (Mark Aldanov), 1971, 1977 (Box-folder 119: 6-9)
  - Shturman, Dora, 1984 (Box-folder 119: 10)
  - Shuba, Anatole, undated (Box-folder 119: 11)
  - Shulman, Marshall D., undated (Box-folder 120: 1)
  - Sick, Gary G., undated (Box-folder 120: 2)
  - Sik, Ota, 1970 (Box-folder 120: 3)
  - Silnitski, Frantishek, 1976 (Box-folder 120: 4)
  - Silvestri, Stefano, undated (Box-folder 120: 5)
  - Simecka, Milan, undated (Box-folder 120: 6)
  - Simis, Konstantin, 1980 (Box-folder 120: 7)
  - Simons, 1971 (Box-folder 120: 8)
  - Sinyavsky, Andrei, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 120: 9)
  - Sirc, Ljubo, 1984 (Box-folder 120: 10)
  - Skolimowski, Henryk, undated (Box-folder 120: 11)
  - Slonimski, Antoni, undated (Box-folder 120: 12)
  - Smith, Paul A., 1971 (Box-folder 120: 13)
  - Smolinski, Leon, 1970 (Box-folder 120: 14)
  - Socor, Vladimitr, 1970 (Box-folder 120: 15)
  - Solchanyk, Roman, 1975 (Box-folder 120: 16)
  - Solovyov, Vladimir and Elena Klepikova, 1980 (Box-folder 120: 17)
  - Solski, W., undated (Box-folder 120: 18)
  - Solymar, Laszlo, 1985 (Box-folder 120: 19)
  - Solzhenistyn, Aleksandr, undated (Box-folder 121: 1-4)
  - Souvarine, Boris, undated (Box-folder 121: 5)
  - Soviet Literature, edited by Max Hayward, 1962 (Box-folder 121: 6)
  - Speaks, undated (Box-folder 121: 7)
  - Spechler, Dina, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 121: 8)
  - Spechler, Martin C., 1981 (Box-folder 121: 9)
  - Sperber, Marie, undated (Box-folder 121: 10)
  - Starza-Smith, A. (translator), 1984 (Box-folder 121: 11)
  - Stefan, Charles G., 1986 (Box-folder 121: 12)
  - Stefanek, Branislav and Zdenek Suda, undated (Box-folder 121: 13)
  - Stehle, Hansjakob, undated (Box-folder 121: 14)
  - Stent, Angela, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 121: 15)
  - Stephenson, Andrew, 1985 (Box-folder 122: 1)
  - St. John, Ronald Bruce, undated (Box-folder 122: 2)
  - Storozynski, Alexander, 1987 (Box-folder 122: 3)
  - Struve, Nikita, 1967 (Box-folder 122: 4)
  - Sturman, Dora, 1984 (Box-folder 122: 5)
  - Stus, Vasyl, undated (Box-folder 122: 6)
  - Sullivan, David S., undated (Box-folder 122: 7)
  - Sulyak, Stephan, 1983 (Box-folder 122: 8)
  - Suny, Ronald Grigor, 1979 (Box-folder 122: 9)
  - Surazska, Wieslawa, 1986 (Box-folder 122: 10)
  - Swidlicki, Andrew, undated (Box-folder 122: 11)
  - Swoboda, V., 1967 (Box-folder 122: 12)
  - Symons, Julian, 1984 (Box-folder 122: 13)
  - Szamuely, Tibor, undated (Box-folder 122: 14)
  - Szczepański, Jan Józef, 1982 (Box-folder 122: 15)
  - Szczypiorski, Piotr, 1985 (Box-folder 122: 16)
  - Szczeplaki, Leslie, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 122: 17)
  - T., Maria, 1983 (Box-folder 122: 18)
  - Tamas, George M., undated (Box-folder 122: 19)
  - Tambs, Lewis A. and Frank Aker, 1982 (Box-folder 122: 20)
  - Tashjean, John E., 1983 (Box-folder 122: 21)
  - Taurer, Bernard, 1984 (Box-folder 122: 22)
  - Tay, Alice Erh-Soon, undated (Box-folder 122: 23)
  - Taylor, Frank, undated (Box-folder 122: 24)
  - Teague, Elizabeth, undated (Box-folder 122: 25)
  - Tellis, Ashley J., 1985 (Box-folder 123: 1)
  - Teodori, Massimo, 1975 (Box-folder 123: 2)
  - Thermos, Elias, 1970 (Box-folder 123: 3)
  - Thomas, Hugh, 1978 (Box-folder 123: 4)
  - Thomas, John R., 1982 (Box-folder 123: 5)
  - Thomas, Raju G. C., undated (Box-folder 123: 6)
  - Thompson, Carlos, 1968 (Box-folder 123: 7)
  - Thomson, Lord, undated (Box-folder 123: 8)
  - Tigrid, Pavel, 1969-1980 (Box-folder 123: 9)
  - Tigrid, Pavel, Revolution Amere, undated (Box-folder 123: 10-11)
  - Tominaga, Ken'ichi, undated (Box-folder 124: 1)
  - Toren, Nina, 1978 (Box-folder 124: 2)
  - Triantis, Stephen G., 1967 (Box-folder 124: 3)
  - Trifonov, Yurii, 1983 (Box-folder 124: 4)
  - Triska, Jan, 1978 (Box-folder 124: 5)
  - Tromp, Bart, 1985 (Box-folder 124: 6)
  - Tsuru, Shigeto, 1971 (Box-folder 124: 7)
  - Tucker, undated (Box-folder 124: 8)
  - Tugwell, Maurice, undated (Box-folder 124: 9)
  - Turchin, Valentin F., undated (Box-folder 124: 10)
  - Turner, Carl B., undated (Box-folder 124: 11)
  - Tütsch, Hans E., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 124: 12)
  - Ukrainian Herald, 1975 (Box-folder 124: 13)
  - Ulmen, G. L., 1982 (Box-folder 124: 14)
  - Unger, Leopold, undated (Box-folder 124: 15)
  - Urban, G. R., 1982-1983 (Box-folder 124: 16-17)
  - Vacic, Aleksander M., undated (Box-folder 125: 1)
  - Vale, Michel, 1980 (Box-folder 125: 2)
  - Valenta, Jiri, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 125: 3)
  - Valentinov, undated (Box-folder 125: 4)
  - Vaughan, Michalina, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 125: 5)
  - Vavilov, N. I., 1975 (Box-folder 125: 6)
  - Vega, Luis Mercier, undated (Box-folder 125: 7)
  - Vertzberger, Ya'acov, undated (Box-folder 125: 8)
  - Victor, Matthew A., undated (Box-folder 125: 9)
  - Viney, Deryck, 1971-1978 (Box-folder 125: 10)
  - Vinokur, Aaron, 1977 (Box-folder 125: 11)
  - Vishniak, Mark, 1970 (Box-folder 125: 12)
  - Vladimir, Markovic, 1986 (Box-folder 125: 13)
  - Voslensky, undated (Box-folder 125: 14)
  - Vrga, Djuro J., 1970 (Box-folder 125: 15)
  - W., undated (Box-folder 125: 16)
  - Wagner, Geoffrey, 1985 (Box-folder 125: 17)
  - Walc, undated (Box-folder 125: 18)
  - Waldron, Arthur N., undated (Box-folder 125: 19)
  - Walesa, Danuta, undated (Box-folder 125: 20)
  - Walesa, Lech, 1985 (Box-folder 125: 21)
  - Walker, P. F., 1975 (Box-folder 125: 22)
  - Walkin, Jacob, 1969-1984 (Box-folder 125: 23)
  - Wapler, Dominique, 1971 (Box-folder 126: 1)
  - Warner, Malcolm, 1969 (Box-folder 126: 2)
  - Wat, Aleksander, 1963 (Box-folder 126: 3)
  - Wedel, Janine, 1986 (Box-folder 126: 4)
  - Weede, Erich, undated (Box-folder 126: 5)
  - Weickhardt, George G., 1984 (Box-folder 126: 6)
  - Weil, Boris, undated (Box-folder 126: 7)
  - Weiner, Robert, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 126: 8)
  - Weissbort, Daniel, 1970 (Box-folder 126: 9)
  - Weeks, Albert L., 1982 (Box-folder 126: 10)
  - Weth, M., 1984 (Box-folder 126: 11)
  - Wesson, Robert G., 1971 (Box-folder 126: 12)
  - Westoby, Adam, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 126: 13)
  - Whelan, Joseph G., 1970-1971 (Box-folder 126: 14)
  - Whetten, Lawrence L., 1972-1978 (Box-folder 126: 15)
  - White, James W., undated (Box-folder 126: 16)
  - White, Lynn, T., 1978-1979 (Box-folder 127: 1)
  - Whitehorn, Alan J., 1971-1972 (Box-folder 127: 2)
  - Whitman, John, 1975 (Box-folder 127: 3)
  - Whyte, Martin King, 1972 (Box-folder 127: 4)
  - Wierzbicki, Piotr, undated (Box-folder 127: 5)
  - Wiles, Peter, undated (Box-folder 127: 6)
  - Willerton, John P., Jr., undated (Box-folder 127: 7)
  - Williams, Frank, undated (Box-folder 127: 8)
  - Wimbush, S. Enders, 1986 (Box-folder 127: 9)
    Regarding an article by Joseph E. Fallon.
  - Wintrop, Norman, 1975 (Box-folder 127: 10)
  - Wishnevsky, Julia, 1985 (Box-folder 127: 11)
  - Witonski, Peter P., 1980-1981 (Box-folder 127: 12)
  - Wohlstetter, Albert, 1969 (Box-folder 127: 13)
  - Wolf, M., undated (Box-folder 127: 14)
  - Wolfe, Bertram, 1970, undated (Box-folder 127: 15-17, 128: 1-3)
  - Woroszylski, Wiktor, undated (Box-folder 128: 4)
  - Worsthorne, Peregrine, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 128: 5)
  - Wraga, Natalia, 1971 (Box-folder 128: 6)
  - Wright, James, 1973 (Box-folder 128: 7)
  - Yakushev, A., undated (Box-folder 128: 8)
  - Yanov, Alexander, 1976 (Box-folder 128: 9)
  - Yodfat, Aryeli Y., 1969-1970 (Box-folder 128: 10)
  - Young, James D., 1968-1986 (Box-folder 128: 11, 129: 1)
  - Zabarah, Mohammed A., 1984 (Box-folder 129: 2)
  - Zagorai, Donald, 1973 (Box-folder 129: 3)
  - Zemstov, I., 1976 (Box-folder 129: 4)
  - Zenko, Franjo, undated (Box-folder 129: 5)
  - Zielinski, Janusz, 1970 (Box-folder 129: 6)
  - Zielonka, Jan, 1984 (Box-folder 129: 7)
  - Zimand, Roman, 1974 (Box-folder 129: 8)
  - Zinam, Oleg, 1970 (Box-folder 129: 9)
  - Zinner, Paul E., 1968 (Box-folder 129: 10)
  - Zubek, Voytek, 1987 (Box-folder 129: 11)
  - Zuzowski, Robert, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 129: 12)
  - Unidentified, circa 1960-1980 (Box-folder 129: 13-14, 130: 1-4)
- Photographs and Slides, 1930-1980
  Includes various photographs of both a professional and personal nature. Also included are slides of the countries that Labedz visited on his personal and professional trips.
  - Book talk, No End Of A Lesson, undated (Box-folder 130: 5)
  - Conferences, 1975, undated (Box-folder 130: 6)
  - Fourth World Congress of Sociology, 1959 (Box-folder 131: 1)
  - Friends and family, circa 1940-1970 (Box-folder 131: 2)
  - German-English Society, undated (Box-folder 131: 3)
  - Labedz, Leopold, circa 1940-1980 (Box-folder 131: 4)
    Includes photographs of Labedz and his family.
  - Labedz, Leopold, visiting Stanford, circa 1980 (Box-folder 131: 5)
  - Labedz, Jakub, 1930-1940 (Box-folder 131: 6)
    Includes portraits of Labedz's father, Jakub.
  - Labedz, Jakub, medical and military service, 1940-1980 (Box-folder 131: 7)
  - Miscellaneous, 1940-1950 (Box-folder 131: 8)
    Includes photographs of art, monuments, buildings, and headshots of unidentified individuals.
  - Negatives, 1950-1980 (Box-folder 131: 9)
  - Protests, undated (Box-folder 131: 10)
  - Slides, 1956-1977
    - Ceylon, 1964 September (Box-folder 131: 11)
    - China, 1976 January (Box-folder 131: 12)
    - Israel, 1964, 1972, 1976 (Box-folder 131: 13)
    - Italy, 1956 September 13 (Box-folder 132: 1)
    - Italy, Switzerland, France, and London, 1956 September 8 (Box-folder 132: 2)
    - Japan, 1977 (Box-folder 132: 3)
    - Mexico, undated (Box-folder 132: 4)
    - Morocco, 1977 September 5 (Box-folder 132: 5)
    - Paris, 1959 April 8 (Box-folder 132: 6)
    - Personal, undated (Box-folder 132: 7)
    - Riviera, 1970 September (Box-folder 132: 8)
    - Rome, 1976 August 22 (Box-folder 132: 9)
    - Scandinavia and Varia, 1964 September 3 (Box-folder 132: 10)
    - Venice, 1970, undated (Box-folder 132: 11)
    - Washington, undated (Box-folder 132: 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964, 1976, undated (Box-folder 132: 13)
      The slides depict scenes from vacations, conferences, events, and the world travels of Leopold Labedz.
- Audiovisual Materials, 1960-1968
  - Pasternak funeral film, 1960
    Access note
    Access copy is available. Use reference ID number 89018_001_r2015.
    Silent black and white film of Boris Pasternak’s funeral, about one minute and three seconds in duration.
  - Sound recordings, 1968, undated (Box 143)
    Sound recordings of various meetings, conferences, and interviews. Some of the sound tape reels are unlabeled.
    - Soviet literature, Oxford, undated
    - Ouvrez les guillemets, Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn, undated; 3.0 sound tape reels
    - Unlabeled, undated
    - Polskie plyty pana Stanislawa, undated
    - Stomma's visit, undated
    - Lisiecka, undated
    - PEN meeting, friend's house, 1968 March 28
    - Plyty Ireny, undated
    - Plyty Laskiego I., undated
    - Interview z Bergerem Szylkosi, undated
    - Unlabeled, undated
    - Unlabeled, undated
    - Zurich 1, Saturday, morning, June 13, [1970]
      Refer to Box 49, Folder 2 for corresponding conference file.
    - Zurich 3, Saturday, afternoon, [1970]
    - Zurich 5, Sunday, morning, June 14th, [1970]
    - Reel transcripts, undated (Box-folder 132: 14-16)
    - Notebook, undated (Box-folder 133: 1)
      Notes go with the Zurich sound recordings 1, 3, and 5.
- Printed Matter, 1938-1986
  - Absees: Soviet and East European Abstract Series, 1969 (Box-folder 133: 2)
  - Aim Report, 1983 (Box-folder 133: 3)
  - Apel na Polski Fundusz Biblioteczny, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 133: 4)
  - "Arbeitstagung von Beirat und Redaktion der Enzyklopädie Sowjetysystem und Demokratische Gessellschaft,", 1965 September (Box-folder 133: 5)
  - Archiwum Współczesne, 1984 (Box-folder 133: 6)
  - "Aus Politik und Zeit geschichte,", 1964 (Box-folder 133: 7)
  - Biblioteka Rewolucyjnego Marksizmu, undated (Box-folder 133: 8)
  - Bieńkowski, Władysław, Motory i Hamulce Socjalizmu, 1969 (Box-folder 133: 9)
  - "British and American Professors in Defence of Persecuted Ukrainian Intellectuals,", circa 1970 (Box-folder 133: 10)
  - Christmas Is a Jewish Holiday, pamphlet, undated (Box-folder 133: 11)
  - "Co każdy aktywista partyjny powinien wiedzieć o dywersji ideologicznej,", 1971 (Box-folder 133: 12)
  - "Conflict Studies,", 1972 (Box-folder 133: 13)
  - Craxi, Bettino, Una Nave e L'Italia, 1985 (Box-folder 133: 14)
  - Czerwony Sztandar, 1974 (Box-folder 133: 15)
  - Dokumentation EPD, newsletter, 1972 (Box-folder 133: 16)
  - "Errata,", 1966 (Box-folder 133: 17)
  - l'Etincelle, 1964 (Box-folder 133: 18)
  - Facts and Observations, 1975 (Box-folder 133: 19)
  - Forum: przegląd prasy światowej, 1967 (Box-folder 133: 20)
  - Forum Service, 1963 (Box-folder 133: 21, 134: 1)
  - Frederick A. Praeger news release, undated (Box-folder 134: 2)
  - "The Ghost of Stalin,", undated (Box-folder 134: 3)
  - "Gielb, Henryk, Więzienia Gen. Franco,", 1946 (Box-folder 134: 4)
  - Great Soviet Encyclopedia, informational pamphlet, 1973 (Box-folder 134: 5)
  - Herald of the Moscow University, 1967 (Box-folder 134: 6)